# **Shilvia Seprianty**

silviasprianty12@gmail.com | 085267483968 | linkedin.com/in/shilvia-seprianty

## **SUMMARY**

Bachelor of Management graduates have a highly motivated social media specialist with a strong enthusiasm for analysis, content creation and administration. Skilled in time management, creativity and attention to detail with a proactive approach to problem-solving and a dedication to continuous learning.

## **EDUCATION**

Purwadhika School Aug 2024 - Present

Digital Marketing

Universitas Bandar Lampung | Manajemen | IPK : 3.96 Sept 2020- Mar 2024

Bachelor of Marketing Management

## **WORK EXPERIENCES**

#### Administration | PT Cipta Darma Sejahtera

Jan 2022 - Present

PT Citra Darma Sejahtera is a company partnering with Pertamina, Indonesia's state-owned oil and natural gas corporation, to distribute LPG (Liquefied Petroleum Gas) subsidies to underprivileged communities in Lampung.

- Responsible and contributing to the operation of company administration through data input and organized archive management.
- Responsible for checking daily transactions.
- Responsible for creating internal and external reports both daily and monthly.

#### Social Media Manager | BDOC

Apr 2021 - Present

BDOC is a Buddhist community dedicated to exploring and practicing Buddhism through hands-on experiences. We host engaging weekly events and share interesting content designed for everyone, regardless of their background or beliefs. Our Instagram: instagram.com/bdoc.id/

- Collaborate with a team lead, 2 designers, and 2 writers to execute a social media strategy on Instagram
- Manage a content calendar to ensure consistent posting frequency.
- Write, design and post monthly (stories and feeds)
- Contribute as a Reels talent, leveraging storytelling to achieve growth in video views and overall engagement.

### **CERTIFICATION**

Intro to Digital Marketing | Purwadhika SchoolJun 2024Mini Course UI Design For Mobile Application | Createcrack.idAug 2024Social Media Marketing | HubSpot AcademyNov 2024

# **SKILL**

**Technical Skills:** Photoshop, Canva, Microsoft Office, ChatGPT Prompt Generator, Figma **Other Skills:** Presentation, Communication, Storytelling, Teamwork, Time Management, Leadership, Content Strategy